whatsonjinan.com 2014-06-16

# Policy - What's On Jinan

**WOX  Jinan Privacy Policy **

The following discloses our private (personal) information protection and dissemination practices:  

**What  is personal information? **  
Personal information is private information which individual person considers privilege and would not want to reveal to a third party. Personal information is personal details which are about an individual whose identity is apparent or can reasonably be ascertained from the information.  

**How  do we collect personal information? **  
Where practical, this site www.whatsonjinan.com (WOX Jinan or WOJ) will collect personal information directly from you. Generally this will be collected by us when you deal with us either in person, by telephone, letter, facsimile, email or when you visit our website. We may request information about you when you make enquires; when you enter competitions, register for promotions, when you request brochures or other information or when you register in this site as a member or user. We may also collect information when we invite you to complete surveys or provide us with feedback.

**Information  collection and use **  
Information obtained is strictly for the website and will be kept in our database to serve you. The database is highly protected and will not be passed to a third party or parties unless with your consent. Old information will be from time to time deleted when you no longer use What's On Jinan. What's On Jinan will never sell this privilege information to anyone. We will take all necessary steps to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with our privacy policy.  

We may also use your contact details to inform you of our information including special events that we think may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your contact information please let us know in an email to editor@whatsonjinan.com. We do not pass details of your personal information to any third party. 

**Opt-out  **  
Should you no longer wish to receive information on services we think may be of interest to you or participate in market research, kindly e-mail us on editor@whatsonjinan.com 

**Feedback  / Complaints **  
We welcome your inquiries or comments about our Policy. Should you have any comments or complaints please contact us at editor@ whatsonjinan.com. 

**Contacting  us **  
In using What's On Jinan, you consent to the collection and use of the information in the ways described above. If you have any questions or comments about these privacy policies, the practices of this site or your dealings with the site please email us at editor@ whatsonjinan.com.
